You son of a bitch!
What have you done to my daughter?
You've had too much.
Please get some rest.
You are right that I'm drunk,
but not drunk enough to rest.
- Let it go, Mom.
- Please, Mom.
Please...
I'm saying this as your family member.
You need to back off for your daughters' sake.
It is not helpful for daughters
to have an aggressive mother.
You son of a bitch!
Don't talk to my mom that way!
Gee, did you just see that?
This is how she is.
How can she do that,
no matter how angry she gets?
Was she like this from the beginning?
It's you who made her that way.
She was as gentle as anyone could be.
She was studying to go to college
while she was working as a nurse's aide.
If you hadn't talked her into it
she wouldn't be like this now.
Change her back to the way she was, bastard!
She was not a minor when she met me.
She was well capable of
making her own decisions.
You may not know it.
She was the one who came on to me first.
She would smile at me
and make herself available.
You were her boss.
Would she possibly have
an attitude towards you?
You should have nothing to say.
How could you possibly
hit on your employee?
It wasn't like that.
I liked the fact she was innocent then.
I loved her!
Stop sounding like a kid who breaks dolls and
tosses them away out of boredom!
What the hell!
Why did you get in the middle?
Let me be the bad guy.
I couldn't help it.
He's been saying that all along
since the wedding.
It's not good for a woman
to be headstrong and stubborn.
Being a headstrong woman should stop with me.
- Did I go too far?
- No.
I would have wanted to do that, too.
Shall we have a little more?
After Mom goes to bed, let's do that...
just two of us.
You...
I will blow you away, Ki Joong.
How are you going to blow me away?
Are you trying to pull one of your stunts on me?
Impressive!
- Do you want some?
- No, thanks.
How are you going to blow me away?
Do this one.
Work with my father.
He will probably drive you nuts.
No, I won't.
I thought about it.
It will be too stressful to mix
business with emotions.
Your father seems to know
what went on between us.
Will he leave me alone?
Without a doubt...
You are good at getting yourself
out of a tough situation.
Did you tell Jung Hoon that you liked him?
No.
I'm a friend to everybody.
I guess I'm not that attractive as a woman.
You have no idea how sexy you are.
Do you know how hard it is for a guy like me
to go steady for five years?
Why did you dump me then?
Let's get that one straight.
You left me. I didn't dump you.
You didn't ask me to stay.
It means you dumped me.
You can't handle my family.
You couldn't even handle your own family.
The reason I didn't ask you to stay
was that I cared about you.
Do you show that you care in the opposite way?
Do you want to ride the motorcycle?
I'm getting married next weekend.
I know that.
I understand that you
got to love Jung Hoon.
Why do you say that now?
Because you keep creating
difficult situations for yourself.
When you are in a cold place
it's understandable that you want to go
somewhere warm to relax.
But it's not where you should be.
Isn't it enough that you got hurt by me?
Do you even know that you hurt me?
I do.
The one who has been hurt
tends to hurt others.
Too complicated!
Although I pushed you away
and let Jung Hoon in
you just won't get out of my mind.
Right now...
I'm about to do something bad.
Something very bad.
Will you forgive me?
Here I come.
Did you know that it snowed yesterday?
We don't have the romance any more,
which is important to a couple.
It's not fair to think this is the first snow.
I've been waiting for an hour because we
promised to meet when we had the first snow.
I didn't know this was the first snow.
Snow should be coming down a lot harder.
Even if it's little, it is the first snow.
I wanted to spend this moment with you.
I was listening to the weather forecast everyday.
Can you hear my heart beat?
I was also listening to the
weather forecast everyday.
It's a lie.
It's the truth.
- Were you cold?
- Yes, very much.
I'm sorry.
To happiness.
- What does it mean?
- A happy life.
I wish you happiness as well.
Hae Jin, Cinderella doesn't exist.
Why did Cinderella drop her glass slipper
and end up being with the prince?
Some say she meant to drop the slipper...
in order to bait him.
Maybe I did the same thing.
I looked up to Dong Gun, when we just met.
I thought he was living in a different world.
In fact, he was from a different world.
He was intelligent, handsome, and nice.
He would take me out
to the best restaurants and all.
If I could have him,
I would have wanted to do anything.
Mom stepped in.
Without her, I would not
have become Cinderella.
Mom, I'm always like this in this house.
I am always alone in this house,
just like I was before.
I miss those days instead.
There was a hope that it would be over
when she returns.
I thought a guy with years of education
and money would be a decent person.
How could I have known
that he would be like this?
If you live as a wife of a rich man
I thought you wouldn't have to worry
about money anymore.
Who would have guessed it would be like this?
If I had known it would be like this
I shouldn't have pushed her into this marriage.
Because they say that the daughter
continues her mother's life...
I tried my hardest not to let that happen.
One of them divorced.
The other broke up right before the wedding.
Mom, you are right.
Love doesn't mean much.
Reality is stronger than love.
Jung Hoon is such a nice guy.
His father is very nice, too.
They will be given a house by his parents.
They can just cover expenses.
Why did they break up saying it's hard?
No matter how strong reality is
can it be stronger than them
wanting to start a life together?
- Hae Yoon.
- Yes?
I have no regrets though.
The fact that I loved my husband.
While I was in love with him
I love the feelings I had during that time.
If you love him, don't give up.
Even though the divorce
sometimes can be inevitable
you should just go with the flow.
Hae Jin.
It's just that...
unlike what I thought
I am such a coward.
Why is she sleeping on her stomach?
It would be hard for her to sleep like that.
- She even turns around in her sleep.
- I know!
So are you still in touch with your second ex-wife?
She calls me to borrow money.
Her husband must not be doing well.
Do you lend her money then?
I sometimes lend her some.
There are times when I don't.
By the way
your parents passed away very early.
When my mom passed away
I even thought about dying myself.
You can never do that!
If it hadn't been for my sister, something could have happened.
When my brother-in-law passed away, it was a nightmare.
Why do people I love have to die on me?
I thought it was because of me.
So it made it hard for me to like someone.
Fool.
You are right.
I'm a fool.
It's bright outside.
It must be morning.
Already?
We must have talked all night.
Gee, it feels like it's only been an hour.
Your eyes look bad.
You have deep dark circles.
Your dark circles are so deep that you look like a panda.
Then that makes us a pair of pandas.
When are we ever going to do it then?
No way.
Never after we drink.
Not until I lose some weight.
Why are you cooking with your jacket on?
Deul Rae is home alone.
I am going to stop by on my way to the store.
Mom, are you ready?
Why are you rushing as well?
Mom drove Deul Rae's car here.
I'm going to get a ride from her.
Let's eat first and then go.
Have breakfast and then go.
Why am I doing this in my own house?
Oh my goodness!
Don't you knock?
I'm sorry.
Mom, tell me what you like to eat.
I will have it ready.
It's okay. I will be back this evening.
You take care of yourself.
We will see you later.
- Okay. Be careful.
- Okay.
I guess you're ecstatic.
Do you want breakfast?
I won't eat what you make.
Suit yourself.
I haven't seen this car before.
Why is it parked here?
I have no idea.
Gee, it's snowing a lot.
What should I do with her?
You should grill her.
I will go in.
I don't want her to be embarrassed.
Should I throw a bucket of water on them?
No, I will have to clean up the floor then.
Deul Rae!
Deul Rae, your big sister is here.
Deul Ja? She shouldn't be here.
She's already here.
Really?
Oh my God! Deul Ja!
Wake up!
Hi, my Deul Rae!
My sister is here.
Oh, Deul Ja.
I thought you would go straight to the store.
If I had, I would have missed this great sight.
Nothing happened.
It's true. Nothing happened.
I'm serious. Trust me.
Break up with him!
When he spent all night with a woman
what would you do with a man who couldn't do anything?
I could have.
That's right. He could have.
We were just too busy talking.
It's not even funny.
I guess you two old people are in love.
- Mr. Tofu.
- Yes?
- Please leave.
- Huh?
Just go home.
I just woke up and am not myself yet.
Go outside and wake up.
I don't want you to see her any more.
Why don't you want me to see her?
I agree. Why not see him?
Can you not ride a motorcycle?
I can't see her living with
a knot of tension in her stomach.
I'm okay. I've ridden one before.
It's not as dangerous as it looks.
Then let's not see each other anymore.
Deul Ja!
I want to formally introduce myself to you.
It's okay.
Why would I want to get respect
from an old man like yourself?
I don't like it.
It makes me feel old.
I felt the same way at first, but it grew on me.
He only looks older.
But he is seven years younger than me.
- He's seven years younger than you?
- Yes.
But he's still over 40.
When a man is over 40, you become
sick of even the man you have been with.
I own a building.
You own a building?
In what area?
- In Jung Reung.
- Oh, that's nice.
- I also own some land in Ee Chon.
- That's nice, too.
Did I pass then?
You've been rejected.
Why? He says he has a lot of money.
These days, I change my mind on life
twelve times per day.
I don't have a conclusion yet.
Money isn't everything.
You are trying to break us apart,
aren't you?
Did you not see Hae Jin?
Nam Do Hyun had the looks, family, and money.
He had everything.
What was it good for?
He had a bad personality.
I'm not going to judge based on only what I can see.
Why do you start to apply that rule on me?
Anyway, motorcycle is out of the question.
If you want to see her, sell that motorcycle.
Then we will talk.
You have to ride the motorcycle.
I can't go against my sister.
Let's not see each other for now.
If we don't see each other...
we can talk on the phone or video chat.
But I can't touch you that way.
Then what can we do?
Shall I sell the motorcycle?
No, I don't want that.
You should live the way you want.
I don't want you to change your life style,
because of me.
Deul Rae!
I like the way you are.
Mommy, can I also have that?
It's not good to have instant food for breakfast.
How about Daddy?
He's grown up, so it's okay.
Here we have the kalbi that you like.
It's good. You also like it, Daddy.
I'm okay.
Have some.
Because you are giving it to me
I will have it.
I'm done.
We will go brush your teeth then.
I think a cat has come inside
the dining room.
What happened to all the kalbi here?
Why don't you ask the cat?
I spoiled you so much that it will be hard
for you to live alone.
Don't kid yourself!
Do Hyun.
There were times when things were good.
I gave birth to our child.
We have a child together.
You said it right.
We have a child and
there were some good times.
It was you who wanted to go through
with this divorce.
You are the one who started this fight.
Did you forget that you started
seeing another woman?
You are the one who
broke off our marriage.
Are you getting mad because I wanted a divorce
after you already broke the marriage?
Does it make sense?
You always say that you are
the victim in this marriage.
In our marriage, I felt alone.
There were so many times when I felt alone.
That's not my fault, but your personality.
I have to be responsible for it?
If we are a couple
you and I loved each other more
than others did and got married.
It should have been different.
You are like this every time.
I am the one who has to do well.
That is wrong.
We both have to do well.
So?
It's too late for us.
One person has given all she had.
It's your turn now, but...
you only want to receive.
That's why we should end it.
So?
Let's not fight over it.
Let's have a divorce by consent.
Let's not have our marriage
judged by others.
If you give me the parental rights and custody
I will agree to your terms on division of property.
Because it doesn't look good
you are trying to give in.
I won't give up Tae Won.
Do Hyun.
We shouldn't have gotten married.
Why are you nibbling on your food?
It makes it uncomfortable to watch you.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
I will come to your work today.
Let's go to the department store.
I will buy you the watch
you talked about before.
It's okay. I already have a watch.
I promised to go help Dong Bi
open her company later.
I told you not to hang out with her.
I'll take care of it.
Where were you last night?
Could you just leave me alone
for now, please?
I'm just so frustrated.
It will be strange if he's all okay now.
Give him some time until he gets better.
- Try this.
- You can leave it there.
You are so funny.
Why aren't you even looking at me?
I don't feel well.
Do I have to force myself
to do fake things to you?
Did I say you should?
You don't seem like the son
I used to know.
What has happened to my son?
Don't whine like a kid.
Your charm works for Dad, not me.
Look at you. You with your temper.
Your charm again?
Can you smile once?
Why do you sigh when I ask you to smile?
A little bit more.
I'm obviously being passed over as a woman.
Okay. Let yourself suffer
as much as you like.
What is it?
It's Ki Joong.
He's inviting me over to the bachelor party.
Things are working out well for him.
You should be getting married like Ki Joong.
Here you are.
Is this the wedding magazine?
- Kim Se Jin?
- Yes.
Please come in.
Were we really chosen as the winner?
Yes.
Because we have been picked
you are not thinking about
selling us some stuff, are you?
No, that's not it.
Why did you think that?
Actually, we are just an ordinary couple.
We don't have any great stories to tell.
That's why you were chosen.
Because we are filled with
too many stories these days.
I don't want to do business
by making them cry.
Those couples will be found by others.
Is that why you found...
people like us who are having
a hard time with jobs
and whose parents are in the middle class?
That's right.
What kind of wedding do you want to have?
People say truth will prevail.
Why does my truth
bounce off the wall every time?
How do you like it?
Do you like it?
On the wedding day,
you will have them buttoned.
Come whenever you want.
Even if you think it's too late, come.
Did you get your tuxedo?
Yes. Are you done with pilates?
Yes. The interior of the house
will be done early next week.
That's good.
Let's get our own clothes
to wear on our honeymoon.
Okay.
- What are you doing tonight?
- I'm having a bachelor party.
Are you? Tomorrow I have plans with my friends.
- All right then. See you.
- See you.
Yes, Father.
Are you now satisfied?
I got it.
Yes, you can wire the money
to that account.
Yes.
All right then.
Too complicated.
Although I pushed you out
and let Jung Hoon in...
I can't get you out of my mind.
Min Ho!
Oh, long time.
You still have your pants hemmed.
- Nice to see you.
- You too.
Did you reflect on yourself last time?
Reflect on what?
About not opening your wallet.
Oh, that?
Do you want to hang out today?
No, I was just reminded of someone.
Where are you?
Yes.
I can't hear you well because
it's too noisy there.
- I've come to Ki Joong's bachelor party.
- Have you?
Have fun!
But I don't feel like staying here, all of a sudden.
If so, do you want to come here?
Is it okay to come?
You said you were busy.
Come over.
Okay.
You are so popular.
Why didn't you bring her in?
I'm not dead, Do Hyun.
That's right. You are very alive.
All of you stay out tonight.
You sound like you are getting married.
You seem so happy.
From tomorrow, you won't be single.
Congrats!
Congratulations!
Well, I don't know if I should be celebrating.
- Aren't you going to meet the girls?
- Sure!
Bring them in.
Let's not do the girls tonight.
Let's just drink first.
Why are you doing this?
It's Ki Joong's bachelor party.
What does it mean?
We should definitely have girls.
This doesn't feel right yet.
Let's hang first... just us.
We are good.
Jung Hoon, I'm saying this
because I'm really worried.
Think again about your marriage.
She's your mother-in-law after all.
How can you say that to me every time?
What mother-in-law?
I'm getting a divorce.
It's been a long time since
things went cold between us.
We are in the middle of
a divorce suit now.
She didn't tell you that?
She didn't, did she?
Her senior is my wife's lawyer.
He's such an impudent guy.
I'm not crazy about my
future mother-in-law, either.
It's still not right to do that
to someone of her age.
You are going to regret later
not listening to me.
You are drunk. Stop it.
He is being cocky.
I said it for his own sake.
Advice can become violent
if it's done wrong.
Even you are doing that?
Are you taking his side?
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
- Why are you acting this way?
- I want to go.
Jung Hoon.
How arrogant!
Aren't you going to listen to me?
Try to understand.
He's very stressed out these days.
They have been having problems
for so long.
Then why did he cheat on her?
Now he's blaming his mother-in-law instead.
You bastard, what do you think you know?
How well do you know my mother-in-law?
Let go.
Let go, man.
He's drunk. Let's go.
He has nothing to do with it.
I'm going crazy.
What kind of bachelor party is this?
Where is Min Ho?
He's the only one for me.
Say ah.
- Wait.
- Why?
- I will wipe it for you.
- No way.
You are just too pretty.
- One more?
- One more fry.
I wonder why things get ugly in a marriage.
Let's go home.
Jung Hoon.
I have a favor to ask.
This is a bribe to ask me
to be nice to Dong Bi.
That's right.
I won't be able to do the same like I used to.
Why not?
On the day we broke up,
I was having a hard time.
I ended up being drunk and sleeping at Dong Bi's place.
When I woke up with a strange feeling
Hae Yoon was looking at me.
I was naked.
- Did you sleep with her?
- No!
Is it even possible
when all she thinks about is you only?
Anything is possible.
You are being cynical, again.
Anyway, what must have Hae Yoon
felt after seeing it?
Whenever I hang out with Dong Bi,
I remember everything.
Then Dong Bi lost Hae Yoon and...
even you. She won't have anybody then.
Hae Yoon lost Dong Bi and me.
She doesn't have anyone, either.
Dong Bi has just suffered from death in her family.
I want you to be there for her.
That's okay.
I don't want to go in.
Why would I run away?
This is my house.
I will kick them all out.
- Why are you still up?
- I was waiting for you.
Oh, my sweetie.
- You still sound like a kid after all these years.
- I agree.
I have you all to myself.
I feel sorry for Hae Yoon.
Come out, Jung Hae Jin!
Mrs. Jung!
- I will tell him to go to sleep.
- Let him be.
Why would you respond to him?
This is my house.
Why are you here in my house?
Is this the only room in the house?
You can go sleep in the office.
Why don't you go sleep outside?
I will sleep in here.
You don't have manners, do you?
No matter how drunk you are, how
can you do this when I'm about to sleep?
And you turn around and blame me for everything?
If you are drunk, go to sleep quietly.
I'm not drunk.
If you are not, you should go to sleep in your office.
It's not comfortable to sleep on the couch.
Then are you telling me to go sleep there instead?
I see.
I will go sleep there then.
Jung Hoon is a son of a bitch!
What are you talking about?
Did you see him tonight?
Yes, I did.
Why did you see him?
Why? I told him not to get married.
I should be the only victim to your mother.
But he wouldn't listen to me.
He's such a bastard!
It tastes good because you gave it to me.
I will be glad to eat anything
you make me.
What brings you here?
We went out on a date.
The more I think about it,
he's too good to lose.
Jung Hoon is the one for Hae Yoon.
What are you mumbling about?
- What about that jerk?
- He's asleep.
He's just a piece of work.
I get to think about a lot of things, because of that man.
It sounds like he mentioned something about you to Jung Hoon.
I guess he wouldn't budge.
If you agree with the one who
badmouths about his mother-in-law
is that a human?
He has no backbone. He breaks up
with her just because she says so.
It's not that he has no backbone.
You heard that he wouldn't listen to him.
Then why can't he get a hold
of a woman's heart?
Why did she have to tell him to break up?
It might have been his mother.
Hae Yoon was stressed out over the
wedding presents and the new house.
If so, that makes him a loser.
If he can't even protect his woman from
his mother, how can he get married?
He has no sense of responsibility.
I wasn't going to do anything.
I can't just stay quiet
because it's too upsetting.
Hello, Mrs. Jung.
Why did you run?
I thought you might be waiting.
I'm sorry. I should've come to see you first.
What was it that you wanted to tell me first?
I'm sorry.
Are you going to keep saying sorry?
Was it a fling to you?
It wasn't.
If not?
When people get stressed over the wedding
preparations, they might want to just break up.
Couldn't you ask her to stay with you?
Don't you know that saying 'let's break up'
means 'hold onto me'?
I couldn't hold onto her.
Why not?
She said she wasn't happy when she was with me.
That's why I couldn't stop her from leaving me.
Why did you not keep her happy then?
I'm sorry.
I'm hurting inside, too.
I should've done more for you.
It's just that I'm not good enough.
If that's how you feel, go get her.
If I could, I would've done it a hundred times.
Until she changes her mind
I can't do anything.
Mrs. Jung.
From the beginning, it was all about
how we felt about each other.
I'm waiting...
for her to fix things on her own
and come back.
Come over here.
I called a cab for you.
Okay.
Please get in.
Please take her to her destination.
Call me any time.
Okay.
Here, try some.
You called me here to make me this?
You said you wanted to have home-made dishes.
Home-made dishes always include kimchi.
You are right.
Is it good?
- It's not good.
- It's not?
When you add a can of tuna in kimchi stew,
doesn't it make it good?
It depends on what kind of kimchi.
It wasn't home-made, was it?
How can I make kimchi at home?
It's too hard.
It's better to buy it.
If you are going to do something like this,
don't call me over.
I will go to a restaurant.
Aren't you going to eat it?
I'm busy. I have to go.
Oppa, do you know something?
What?
You are older than my father.
Are you saying that to make me feel responsible?
I will go to cooking school.
I will try hard.
I will do better than your current wife.
Why do you like such a bad guy like me?
At first, it was your money.
Right now, I have nowhere else to go to.
It's good that you are honest.
I've looked into it.
It turns out the investigator divorced,
because of her husband's affair.
I see.
Next time, try to emphasize...
that your husband's affair
broke off your marriage.
Would it really work?
If you stress that his affair is habitual
it could make it less noticeable
that you were once the other woman.
- I understand.
- Don't be intimidated.
Thank you.
By the way, when is your mother going to invite me over?
Don't wait for her to invite you over.
Why don't you visit her this weekend?
You will see Hae Yoon, too.
Your mother seems tough.
If I show up uninvited,
she may not like it.
Then ask Hae Yoon.
Oh, that's an idea.
All right then.
Where is her cosmetics store?
Here you are.
- Can I pay with my credit card?
- Yes, you can.
But I would love it if it's paid in cash.
It's tough to deal with the service charges.
It's only 18,000 won.
Here it is.
Thank you. Please come again.
- Sure. See you.
- See you.
Hello, Mrs. Jung.
What brings you here?
I just had a meeting with Jung Hae Jin.
And I was in the area and thought of you.
Please have this. I got it in Gangnam.
Thank you.
It looks so good.
Mrs. Jung. I'm the real deal.
I already know that.
Considering you were a big part of matching
Nam Do Hyun and Jung Hae Jin
I'm the perfect one for your second son-in-law.
I like the fact that you are very clear.
The more time you spend, the more you will like me.
I'm the type who does that.
There is one thing I'm curious about.
Please ask me.
I really like how direct you are.
Why do you want to marry my Hae Yoon?
Although you don't have the look,
you are a lawyer.
I'm sure a lot of women
want to chase you for it.
I'm just a bit short, but...
I am not bad-looking.
I felt something when I saw
Hae Yoon with Jung Hoon.
She is very faithful.
She wouldn't even budge
even if I tried to hit on her.
She pushed such temptation like me away.
I knew that about her in the past.
I've become convinced this time.
He has potential to be a cheater.
He has a way with his words.
What does she think of you?
I haven't told her yet.
I wanted to tell you first.
How come?
Because you are the center of her universe.
I realized that you are the one
who holds it together for her.
Marriage is about two people involved.
I have no power over it.
This sushi is really good.
Please enjoy.
Hello?
Why are you out of breath?
I was just cleaning the bathroom.
I ran into Do Hyun yesterday.
He still hasn't changed much.
He was with that girl.
He has an interesting taste in women now, huh?
She was different from you.
I see.
If there is anything I can help about
the law suit, let me know.
I appreciate it.
But I'm hoping it doesn't get to that.
All right then.
Talk to you later.
Hi, how are you?
I will pay for it.
I understand it's hard
to find a patron these days.
Of course.
I can handle that amount.
I will wire the money right away.
We are redirecting your call...
Sir, your wife is here.
Your lunch break is long.
It's none of your business.
I checked the bank account today.
I thought it was one or two days late,
but the money is not coming in.
It doesn't concern me.
I only sleep in the house.
I make my own food.
Calm down.
Why are you getting mad?
How can I not be mad?
I could lose everything.
You shouldn't be doing this.
Why not?
When you want to divorce me
how can you want to spend
the money I earn?
How can you manage to get
even lower every time?
I can say the same thing for you.
You brought your mother into the house.
You are trying to kick me out
of the house, aren't you?
Send your mother out.
Then I will deposit some
into the bank account.
Do you think you can have it your own way?
What have I not had
my own way so far?
How come I am not getting
what I deserve?
What's going on?
He says he won't deposit his paychecks.
How are we supposed to live?
Don't be too quick to respond.
I told you before.
A divorce suit is like entering hell.
We can submit a form for support fees and child rearing expenses.
It's usually submitted before
the investigation on the property.
The paycheck came in last month as scheduled.
- How much did you get monthly?
- It was 10,000,000 won.
Then we will request for 10,000,000 won.
We won't get the full amount though.
When will that be?
There is going to be a proceeding
and the judge will decide then.
And after the investigation, there will be a trial.
Are you saying that I won't get the money until then?
Yes, I am.
Unless he is willing,
the legal process will take time.
You are right about entering hell.
You go in first.
No, I will come in after you.
Okay.
What's going on?
Congratulations on your upcoming wedding!
Thanks, guys!
We wrote on the card together.
We spent money together for it.
Mrs. Jung, I wish you a happy marriage.
I told you not to use that phrase.
Please come to our wedding
in the future.
If you guys are still together.
Okay.
I won't ask you to stay with me any more.
If you say the life I can offer you...
is sad and a poor reality
how can I possibly ask you
to stay with me?
You are here. Busy?
A little bit.
Here.
You are already starting your business.
Time flies.
Just come during that time.
There is no dress code.
Okay.
Why don't you work it out
with the daughter of president Han?
You said you would take pictures, but didn't show up?
No.
Why did you do that when you are so reliable?
Be friends with her.
She can be a very important connection.
Hi, mom.
What is it that you need to sort out on your own?
Why did you say
you wanted to break up?
What is this about?
I saw Jung Hoon.
Why did you see him?
I told you that it was over.
It is not over.
He was still the same.
You were like a married couple.
It's better to listen to
what other people think.
Please leave him alone.
I wanted to break up
because I wasn't sure.
I thought you would be happy
to hear the news.
He's still an employee at a small company
living paycheck to paycheck.
Look at your sister.
Money isn't everything.
Jung Hoon is a nice guy.
You both will be making money.
If you tighten your belts
you won't become filthy rich, but comfortable.
Jung Hoon...
He can marry a better woman
and live a better life.
If he marries a better woman than you,
then what?
What about you?
Who would you marry then?
Would you marry Attorney Jun?
I don't have to get married.
I knew that you would be like this.
You would grow old as a spinster...
and drive me crazy, I thought.
Where are you going this late?
I have plans tonight.
It is over.
You need to accept it.
You are late.
What is the reason you wanted to see me about?
You didn't have dinner yet, did you?
Let's eat first.
You wanted to see me
to give this to me?
I can't come.
You think you might run into Jung Hoon.
Yes. There will be his parents, too.
Don't do that to Dong Bi.
I think they have had feelings
for each other for a long time.
It's just that they didn't realize it.
Dong Bi now knows how she feels.
Jung Hoon will know
how he feels some day.
It doesn't make sense.
There were times when
their relationship bothered me.
Because she was my best friend and he was my man
I tried to force myself to trust them.
You are really determined
to break up with Jung Hoon.
That's why you are
making up that theory.
I trust Dong Bi.
Even if she was tempted
to hit on Jung Hoon
I trust her.
Can you marry Dong Bi then?
Now she is doing as well as you are.
She has all the potential
to be your match.
Can't you switch your bride-to-be?
I can't do business all by myself.
There are people tangled in it.
I can't change the way now.
If so, stay out of my business.
How can I stay out?
When I leave her side this time
I won't be able to stay by her side again.
You got everything you needed.
You are ready.
The preparation went easier
than I thought.
Wow, it's snowing.
It's the first snow.
It's not the first snow.
It snowed before.
It wasn't that much of snow.
It was just flurries of snow.
I am with you when we are
having the first snow.
Ki Joong asked me to take care of you.
Have you ever loved two people
at the same time?
Is it possible?
I think I might be in love with you.
What?
That joke is not even funny.
If you wanted me to laugh, it worked.
It took me a while to say that.
From now on,
I don't want to deceive myself.
I don't want to hide my feelings, either.
Do you remember that night?
The night I became a companion for you.
I realized it that night.
That you've had a place in my heart for a long time.
What did happen that night?
Think very carefully.
You'll figure it out.
You are being weird.
You've been through a lot lately.
That's why you've become weird.
I'm not being weird.
If you don't like me being this way
I will accept it.
What's going on?
You and I are friends.
I'm not a hog.
I've been too busy to think
about how you guys feel.
I am not going to
sacrifice myself any more.
I haven't had anything to eat
for three days.
I can't stop crying.
How can I possibly forget this guy?
I believe time heals everything.
- Hae Yoon!
- Hi, Deul Rae!
- You've also got this, haven't you?
- No.
She didn't give it to you?
On second thought,
you don't need it between you two.
I don't know what to get for her.
Let's go together.
- I'm not going to go.
- Why not?
I'm busy.
You have to go,
no matter how busy you are.
You are the only friend of Dong Bi's.
Plus, Ki Joong is getting married next week.
She must be feeling very hurt.
You should be there for her.
She and I are not friends any more.
Forget it.
You are the leading character.
I'm the supporting character
who makes you shine.
Who is it?